1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser("")
29. navigateToUrl(URL)
33. maximizeWindow()
37. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
41. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
45. setText(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), "Iphone 11")
49. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
53. custom.ProductHelper.addAnyAvailableProduct()
57. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
61. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
65. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
69. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
73. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
77. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)
81. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/btn_continue"))
85. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), 10)
89. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
93. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
97. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Address"), randomAddress)
105. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
109. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Province"))
113. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
117. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Select Province"))
121. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Khan Chamkar Mon_Select_Province"))
125. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Districts"))
129. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Sangkat Tonle Basak_Districts"))